<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book id="book-001" title="Introduction to Field Service" language="en">
<metadata>
<author>Jane Doe</author>
<publisher>Acme Training</publisher>
<date>2025-12-02</date>
<isbn>978-1-23456-789-0</isbn>
</metadata>

<!-- Chapter 1 -->
<chapter id="ch-01" title="Getting Started">
<intro>
<para>Overview of the system and basic concepts.</para>
</intro>

<section id="ch-01-sec-01" title="Overview">
<subject id="ch-01-sec-01-subj-01" name="System Description">
<pageblock id="pb-0101" type="text">
<heading>What the system does</heading>
<para>The system performs diagnostics and reports status.</para>
</pageblock>

<pageblock id="pb-0102" type="task">
<heading>Initial Power-up Check</heading>
<task id="task-010201" name="PowerOnCheck" level="basic">
<description>Steps to safely power up the unit for first use.</description>

<step number="1">
Ensure power cable is connected.
Make sure the cable is firmly seated on both ends.
Check the plug for any visible damage before using it.
Confirm the socket is rated for the unit's power requirements.
Avoid using loose or extended cables to prevent power drops.
Ensure the environment around the port is dry and clean.
</step>

<step number="2">
Switch on main power.
Verify that the outlet is supplying stable electricity.
Confirm that the power button clicks smoothly without resistance.
Observe any initial LED activity when the unit receives power.
Listen for faint startup sounds indicating internal initialization.
Avoid touching internal parts while power is switching on.
</step>

<step number="3">
Wait for self-test to complete (blinking green).
Watch the LED pattern to ensure it follows the normal cycle.
Avoid interrupting the process by toggling the power switch.
Keep the device steady to prevent vibration-related issues.
Listen for short beeps that may indicate progress.
Allow extra time if the unit is starting for the first time.
</step>

<expectedResult>Unit completes POST and shows ready status.</expectedResult>

<safetyWarnings>
<warning>Do not open the unit while connected to mains.</warning>
</safetyWarnings>

</task>
</pageblock>

</subject>
</section>

<section id="ch-01-sec-02" title="Installation">
<subject id="ch-01-sec-02-subj-01" name="Physical Installation">
<pageblock id="pb-0201" type="text">
<heading>Mounting the unit</heading>
<para>Mount on a flat surface with four M4 screws.</para>
</pageblock>

<pageblock id="pb-0202" type="task">
<heading>Mounting Procedure</heading>
<task id="task-020201" name="MountUnit" level="intermediate">
<description>How to mount the unit safely and securely.</description>

<step number="1">
Mark hole positions on surface.
Use a ruler or template to align hole points accurately.
Ensure the marks form a straight and balanced layout.
Double-check spacing to match the unit’s mounting bracket.
Avoid marking on uneven or unstable surfaces.
Use a pencil or marker that is clearly visible on the material.
</step>

<step number="2">
Drill pilot holes.
Choose a drill bit that matches the recommended size.
Hold the drill steady to avoid widening the hole.
Wear safety glasses to protect your eyes from debris.
Clear dust from the holes after drilling.
Ensure the holes are straight for proper screw alignment.
</step>

<step number="3">
Install screws and tighten to 3 Nm.
Use a torque driver to avoid over-tightening.
Insert each screw gently before applying full torque.
Ensure screws sit flush against the surface.
Check that the unit is firmly secured without wobbling.
Recheck torque settings to ensure uniform tightening.
</step>

<tools>
<tool>Electric drill</tool>
<tool>Torque driver</tool>
</tools>

<estimatedTime unit="minutes">15</estimatedTime>

</task>
</pageblock>

</subject>
</section>
</chapter>

<!-- Chapter 2 -->
<chapter id="ch-02" title="Operation">
<section id="ch-02-sec-01" title="Basic Operation">
<subject id="ch-02-sec-01-subj-01" name="User Interface">
<pageblock id="pb-0301" type="text">
<heading>Front panel overview</heading>
<para>Buttons, LEDs, and ports described.</para>
</pageblock>

<pageblock id="pb-0302" type="task">
<heading>Performing a Self-test</heading>
<task id="task-030201" name="RunSelfTest" level="basic">
<description>Run the built-in self-test routine.</description>

<step number="1">
From the main menu, select Diagnostics &gt; Self-test.
Ensure the screen is responsive before navigating.
Check that the menu icons are displayed correctly.
Use the arrow keys if the touch input is not available.
Wait for the interface to load completely.
Avoid pressing multiple buttons at once to prevent glitches.
</step>

<step number="2">
Confirm 'Start' when prompted.
Review any warning messages shown before starting.
Make sure no ongoing processes may interfere with the test.
Press the confirmation button gently to avoid misselection.
Verify that the prompt matches the expected test name.
Stay near the device in case a user action is needed.
</step>

<step number="3">
Review the results screen for errors.
Read all displayed messages carefully for details.
Scroll through the results page if multiple entries exist.
Compare error codes with the troubleshooting section.
Take a screenshot if logs need to be stored.
Report any unusual patterns for further diagnosis.
</step>

<expectedResult>No errors reported; return code 0.</expectedResult>

</task>
</pageblock>

</subject>
</section>

<section id="ch-02-sec-02" title="Maintenance">
<subject id="ch-02-sec-02-subj-01" name="Routine Maintenance">
<pageblock id="pb-0401" type="task">
<heading>Cleaning Procedure</heading>
<task id="task-040101" name="CleanFilter" level="basic">
<description>Remove dust and debris from the airflow filter.</description>

<step number="1">
Power down and unplug the unit.
Wait a few seconds to ensure internal power fully discharges.
Check the power cord for heat before handling it.
Place the unit on a stable surface during the process.
Avoid touching internal components after shutdown.
Keep the unplugged cable away from wet areas.
</step>

<step number="2">
Remove filter per instructions.
Follow the manual diagram to avoid damaging clips.
Hold the filter bracket firmly while pulling it out.
Inspect the filter for visible wear or cracks.
Keep the removed filter away from dusty environments.
Note any unusual smell or discoloration for future checks.
</step>

<step number="3">
Wash filter with mild detergent, dry completely.
Use lukewarm water for better cleaning efficiency.
Avoid scrubbing too hard to prevent tearing the mesh.
Shake off excess water before leaving it to dry.
Place the filter in an open space with good airflow.
Confirm the filter is fully dry to avoid moisture damage.
</step>

<step number="4">
Reinstall filter and power on.
Insert the filter gently back into its slot.
Make sure it sits flush without bending.
Secure any latches or clips properly.
Plug the power cable back in after installation.
Observe airflow to confirm proper reassembly.
</step>

<safetyWarnings>
<warning>Ensure the unit is completely powered off before opening.</warning>
</safetyWarnings>

</task>
</pageblock>
</subject>
</section>
</chapter>

</book>
